[
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 32, 60, 83, 53?",
    "correctAnswer": "57",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "57",
      "58",
      "59",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 11, 82, 65, 86?",
    "correctAnswer": "61",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "61",
      "62",
      "63"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 26, 8, 74?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 60, 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 37, 2, 77, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "39",
      "40",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 87, 42, 93?",
    "correctAnswer": "74",
    "options": [
      "73",
      "74",
      "75",
      "76"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 15, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 3, 35?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 27, 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 39, 83, 36, 78?",
    "correctAnswer": "59",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "59",
      "60",
      "61"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 63, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "53",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "53",
      "54",
      "55"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 53, 93?",
    "correctAnswer": "73",
    "options": [
      "72",
      "73",
      "74",
      "75"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 72, 41, 61?",
    "correctAnswer": "58",
    "options": [
      "57",
      "58",
      "59",
      "60"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 80, 77, 71?",
    "correctAnswer": "76",
    "options": [
      "75",
      "76",
      "77",
      "78"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 34, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 92, 48, 99, 37?",
    "correctAnswer": "69",
    "options": [
      "68",
      "69",
      "70",
      "71"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 72, 22, 58, 76?",
    "correctAnswer": "57",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "57",
      "58",
      "59"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 88, 29, 19, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "44",
      "45",
      "46"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 20, 43, 49, 32?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 54, 92, 97?",
    "correctAnswer": "81",
    "options": [
      "80",
      "81",
      "82",
      "83"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 32, 89, 95?",
    "correctAnswer": "72",
    "options": [
      "71",
      "72",
      "73",
      "74"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 28, 24?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "27",
      "28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 5, 73, 57, 97?",
    "correctAnswer": "58",
    "options": [
      "57",
      "58",
      "59",
      "60"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 81, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "44",
      "45",
      "46"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 53, 74, 80?",
    "correctAnswer": "69",
    "options": [
      "68",
      "69",
      "70",
      "71"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 67, 71, 20, 22?",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "45",
      "46",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 91, 70, 25?",
    "correctAnswer": "62",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "62",
      "63",
      "64"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 68, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "38",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "38",
      "39",
      "40"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 51, 43, 23?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "39",
      "40",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 69, 78, 35, 58?",
    "correctAnswer": "60",
    "options": [
      "59",
      "60",
      "61",
      "62"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 5, 51, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 55, 56, 81?",
    "correctAnswer": "64",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "64",
      "65",
      "66"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 52, 56?",
    "correctAnswer": "54",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "54",
      "55",
      "56"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 62, 66, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "59",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "59",
      "60",
      "61"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 26, 54, 25?",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "35",
      "36",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 72, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "60",
    "options": [
      "59",
      "60",
      "61",
      "62"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 84, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "62",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "62",
      "63",
      "64"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 88, 65, 72?",
    "correctAnswer": "75",
    "options": [
      "74",
      "75",
      "76",
      "77"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 22, 36, 98?",
    "correctAnswer": "52",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "52",
      "53",
      "54"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 68, 41, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "52",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "52",
      "53",
      "54"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 47, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "33",
      "34",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 58, 22?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "40",
      "41",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 38, 72, 73?",
    "correctAnswer": "61",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "61",
      "62",
      "63"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 89, 79, 54?",
    "correctAnswer": "74",
    "options": [
      "73",
      "74",
      "75",
      "76"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 41, 95?",
    "correctAnswer": "68",
    "options": [
      "67",
      "68",
      "69",
      "70"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 6, 19, 8, 27?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 15, 91, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "40",
      "41",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 84, 86?",
    "correctAnswer": "85",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "85",
      "86",
      "87"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 34, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "27",
      "28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 85, 59?",
    "correctAnswer": "72",
    "options": [
      "71",
      "72",
      "73",
      "74"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 24, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 6, 45, 44, 25?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "31",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 3, 94, 35?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "44",
      "45",
      "46"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 33, 67?",
    "correctAnswer": "50",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "50",
      "51",
      "52"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 8, 66, 70, 24?",
    "correctAnswer": "42",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "43",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 72, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "37",
      "38",
      "39"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 34, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 62, 60, 91, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "54",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "54",
      "55",
      "56"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 20, 72?",
    "correctAnswer": "46",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "46",
      "47",
      "48"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 36, 68?",
    "correctAnswer": "52",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "52",
      "53",
      "54"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 30, 32?",
    "correctAnswer": "31",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "31",
      "32",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 41, 75, 63, 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "46",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "46",
      "47",
      "48"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 89, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "51",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "51",
      "52",
      "53"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 8, 78, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "42",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "43",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 4, 48, 86, 90?",
    "correctAnswer": "57",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "57",
      "58",
      "59"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 45, 2, 97?",
    "correctAnswer": "48",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "48",
      "49",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 42, 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 29, 16, 60, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "28",
      "29",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 31, 5, 69?",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "35",
      "36",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 55, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "34",
      "35",
      "36"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 78, 45, 92, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "64",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "64",
      "65",
      "66"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 91, 35, 8, 34?",
    "correctAnswer": "42",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "43",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 17, 39?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "28",
      "29",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 50, 74?",
    "correctAnswer": "62",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "62",
      "63",
      "64"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 78, 10, 95?",
    "correctAnswer": "61",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "61",
      "62",
      "63"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 96, 98, 69, 37?",
    "correctAnswer": "75",
    "options": [
      "74",
      "75",
      "76",
      "77"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 99, 6, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "39",
      "40",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 12, 66?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "39",
      "40",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 34, 94?",
    "correctAnswer": "64",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "64",
      "65",
      "66"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 89, 40, 36?",
    "correctAnswer": "55",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "55",
      "56",
      "57"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 63, 31, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "47",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "47",
      "48",
      "49"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 79, 95?",
    "correctAnswer": "87",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "87",
      "88",
      "89"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 70, 66, 75, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "65",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "65",
      "66",
      "67"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 79, 99?",
    "correctAnswer": "89",
    "options": [
      "88",
      "89",
      "90",
      "91"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 83, 9, 52?",
    "correctAnswer": "48",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "48",
      "49",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 90, 20?",
    "correctAnswer": "55",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "55",
      "56",
      "57"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 77, 79?",
    "correctAnswer": "78",
    "options": [
      "77",
      "78",
      "79",
      "80"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 2, 24?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 61, 8, 90?",
    "correctAnswer": "53",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "53",
      "54",
      "55"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 19, 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 92, 50?",
    "correctAnswer": "71",
    "options": [
      "70",
      "71",
      "72",
      "73"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 91, 93?",
    "correctAnswer": "92",
    "options": [
      "91",
      "92",
      "93",
      "94"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 93, 55?",
    "correctAnswer": "74",
    "options": [
      "73",
      "74",
      "75",
      "76"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 86, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "49",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "49",
      "50",
      "51"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 84, 15, 36?",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "45",
      "46",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 46, 84?",
    "correctAnswer": "65",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "65",
      "66",
      "67"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 42, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 62, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "55",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "55",
      "56",
      "57"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 5, 39?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average <br> of 83, 87?",
    "correctAnswer": "85",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "85",
      "86",
      "87"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 5, 34, 41, 43, 44?",
    "correctAnswer": "41",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "40",
      "41",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 9, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 9, 26, 42, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "25",
      "26",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 11, 15, 21, 33?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 15, 39, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "38",
      "39",
      "40"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 18, 33, 34, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 13, 21, 24, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "22",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 14, 19, 35, 38?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 10, 12, 24, 31?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 11, 12, 13, 23?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 12, 20, 29, 35, 41, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "28",
      "29",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 20, 25, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "25",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "25",
      "26",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 1, 3, 12, 21, 25, 37, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "20",
      "21",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 1, 28, 31, 36, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "31",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "31",
      "32",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 14, 17?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 15, 30?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 17, 19, 38, 40, 43, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "38",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "38",
      "39",
      "46"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 10, 33, 38?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 5, 47, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "47",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "46",
      "47",
      "48"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 9, 13, 15, 32, 34, 35?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 23, 28, 31?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "27",
      "28",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 8, 21, 23, 24, 29, 37?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 22, 26, 37, 40, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 10, 25, 26, 29, 36, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "27",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 16, 17, 25, 30?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 8, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 32, 33, 39?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 11, 14, 29, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 23, 24, 39, 42, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "39",
      "40",
      "46"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 15, 22, 23, 27, 35, 39, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "27",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "27",
      "28",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 14, 28, 32, 33?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "27",
      "28",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 11, 12, 17, 20, 25, 34, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 22, 24, 33, 44, 46, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "33",
      "34",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 14, 21, 23, 37, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 8, 15?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 20, 21, 31, 37, 42, 44?",
    "correctAnswer": "31",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "31",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 23, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 11, 12, 13, 15, 16, 17, 33?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 18, 23, 24, 28?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 20, 35?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "21",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 16, 28, 29, 34, 37, 40, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "34",
      "35",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 10, 22, 32?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 6, 16, 37, 47, 48, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 10, 19, 23, 27, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 12, 20, 26, 36, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "27",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 27, 31, 34, 39, 43, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "33",
      "34",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 27, 28, 32, 40, 44, 46, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "39",
      "40",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 1, 5, 7, 14, 15, 20, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 10, 14, 27, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 17, 20, 24, 27, 45, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "23",
      "24",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 11, 17, 21, 26, 27, 34?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "20",
      "21",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 29, 33?",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "29",
      "30",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 1, 11, 36?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "48"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 26, 28, 38?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "28",
      "29",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 10, 18, 23, 30, 41, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 31, 32, 40, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "31",
      "32",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 17, 27, 32, 37, 38, 45, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 12, 16, 19, 24, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 12, 21, 23, 31, 35?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 43, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "43",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "42",
      "43",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 20, 23, 34, 38, 39?",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "33",
      "34",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 5, 15, 23, 30, 35, 39, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "29",
      "30",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 10, 19, 21, 25, 34, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "22",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 5, 6, 30, 31, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "29",
      "30",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 11, 16, 26, 28, 42, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "25",
      "26",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 18, 27?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "18",
      "19",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 9, 20, 21, 40?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 11, 20, 32, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 11, 41, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "41",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "40",
      "41",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 1, 9, 21?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 16, 24, 29, 36, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "28",
      "29",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 5, 6, 15, 24, 26, 36, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "24",
      "25",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 30, 44?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "31",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 12, 34, 39, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "33",
      "34",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 17, 38, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "38",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "38",
      "39"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 26, 28?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "27",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 11, 14, 19, 30, 39, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 14, 18, 44, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "17",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 17, 18, 20, 21, 26, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 19, 37, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 21, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "22",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 33, 42?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 6, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "39"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 20, 33?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 8, 9, 25, 47?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 5, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 27, 36?",
    "correctAnswer": "27",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "26",
      "27",
      "28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 19, 20, 36, 38, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "35",
      "36",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 10, 14, 15, 32, 42, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 17, 20, 22, 27, 46, 48?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 4, 12, 14, 26, 36?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 12, 22, 35, 43?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 16, 20, 37, 41, 44, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "37",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "36",
      "37",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 12, 18, 20, 39, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 21, 22, 33, 37?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 10, 33, 35, 47, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "34",
      "35",
      "36"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 9, 11, 13, 18, 35, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 9, 12, 16, 22, 32, 38?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 3, 5, 22, 28, 34, 45, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "27",
      "28",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 25, 31, 35, 39?",
    "correctAnswer": "31",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "30",
      "31",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 4, 4, 18, 4, 19, 4, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 19, 12, 18, 19, 18, 19, 19, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 12, 10, 10, 12, 12, 2, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 17, 2, 2, 2, 12, 12, 17, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 16, 18, 18, 18, 11, 16, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 9, 3, 9, 2, 2, 9, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 3, 13, 3, 1, 1, 13, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 8, 2, 8, 2, 8, 6, 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 15, 5, 9, 5, 5, 5, 15?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 17, 7, 10, 10, 17, 7, 7, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 19, 13, 13, 19, 13, 4, 13, 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 7, 14, 14, 6, 7, 7, 6, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 11, 13, 13, 18, 11, 11, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 9, 14, 14, 14, 14, 11, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 14, 14, 14, 12, 11, 11, 12, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 4, 4, 8, 8, 18, 18, 8, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 3, 3, 4, 1, 3, 4, 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 16, 16, 16, 19, 16, 12, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 16, 4, 17, 16, 4, 4, 4, 17?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 6, 6, 6, 6, 5, 12, 12, 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 14, 18, 11, 18, 18, 14, 18, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 15, 10, 3, 3, 10, 10, 15, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 14, 14, 14, 16, 14, 13, 13, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 8, 19, 8, 8, 8, 2, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 6, 19, 6, 6, 9, 6, 9, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "8",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 4, 4, 4, 9, 10, 4, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 15, 2, 9, 15, 2, 9, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 2, 8, 2, 8, 2, 19, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 18, 12, 6, 12, 12, 12, 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 7, 15, 9, 15, 7, 15, 15?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 14, 8, 3, 8, 14, 14, 3, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 7, 19, 19, 19, 19, 7, 18, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 9, 9, 9, 18, 3, 18, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 15, 17, 17, 15, 11, 11, 11, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 9, 16, 16, 8, 16, 8, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 17, 9, 9, 17, 17, 19, 17, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 5, 19, 12, 19, 19, 5, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 3, 1, 3, 9, 1, 9, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 5, 5, 12, 1, 1, 1, 1, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 6, 18, 3, 6, 6, 6, 3, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 6, 5, 5, 5, 3, 3, 5, 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 6, 6, 7, 7, 1, 6, 6, 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 3, 3, 7, 3, 7, 8, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 10, 10, 1, 12, 10, 1, 10, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 9, 15, 15, 13, 9, 13, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 16, 8, 2, 2, 16, 8, 8, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 19, 12, 19, 1, 1, 12, 19, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 18, 14, 11, 11, 11, 11, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 12, 13, 13, 11, 13, 11, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 13, 12, 12, 12, 13, 12, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 16, 16, 10, 8, 16, 10, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 13, 13, 13, 9, 9, 19, 19, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 15, 8, 8, 18, 18, 15, 8, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 10, 10, 12, 9, 12, 9, 10, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 8, 7, 2, 2, 2, 8, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 9, 12, 8, 9, 9, 8, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 15, 17, 17, 15, 15, 15, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 15, 3, 3, 15, 15, 15, 4, 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 10, 12, 13, 12, 10, 12, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 19, 16, 16, 19, 19, 5, 5, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 17, 11, 17, 9, 9, 9, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 16, 5, 16, 5, 8, 16, 8, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 19, 6, 5, 19, 19, 19, 5, 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 5, 17, 19, 5, 17, 17, 17, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "17",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 17, 17, 18, 18, 9, 18, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 8, 18, 18, 18, 16, 18, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 10, 12, 10, 12, 6, 6, 10, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 7, 15, 7, 7, 16, 15, 7, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 1, 14, 2, 1, 14, 1, 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 8, 17, 8, 17, 7, 8, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 3, 11, 7, 7, 3, 7, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 12, 12, 3, 6, 6, 12, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 16, 3, 16, 16, 16, 8, 8, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 18, 9, 18, 9, 18, 18, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 14, 10, 3, 10, 10, 3, 10, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 18, 4, 18, 4, 8, 18, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 5, 10, 6, 5, 6, 5, 5, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 2, 19, 3, 19, 2, 3, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 16, 3, 16, 16, 19, 19, 16, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 4, 10, 18, 4, 10, 4, 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 15, 15, 2, 13, 13, 15, 15?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 8, 8, 8, 3, 2, 2, 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 15, 9, 15, 15, 18, 18, 15, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 4, 2, 14, 4, 4, 4, 2, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 7, 7, 14, 7, 3, 7, 3, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 3, 9, 3, 5, 5, 5, 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 7, 7, 12, 12, 7, 16, 16, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 10, 10, 3, 10, 14, 14, 3, 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 17, 9, 8, 17, 8, 17, 17?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 19, 1, 19, 12, 19, 1, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 4, 4, 18, 11, 18, 18, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 7, 7, 7, 17, 7, 17, 18, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 15, 3, 14, 15, 15, 14, 15, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 16, 2, 2, 17, 17, 16, 16, 16?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 14, 14, 14, 19, 8, 8, 14, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "16",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 2, 2, 10, 10, 2, 2, 19, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 17, 16, 17, 5, 16, 17, 5, 17?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 13, 13, 14, 14, 8, 8, 13, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 18, 16, 18, 11, 16, 11, 11?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 8, 13, 13, 1, 13, 1, 13?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "13",
      "14",
      "15"
    ]
  }
]